Guide to the J.G. Link and Company Records 1939-1965
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
J.G. Link and Company Records
1939-1965
Montana State University-Bozeman Library, Merrill G Burlingame Special Collections P.O. Box 173320 Bozeman, MT 59717-3320 United States Phone (406) 994-4242 Fax (406) 994-2851 http://www.lib.montana.edu/archives/ University Archivist spcoll@www.lib.montana.edu
Collection 2403, MtBC, us
J.G. Link and Company
23 linear feet
The J.G. Link and Company Records consist of photographic images of various building projects, Elmer F. Link’s personal diaries, routine office files and project files. The photographs are either images of the building themselves or of drawings. The diaries are day records of Elmer F. Link. The office files document the day to day operation of the firm, mostly for its Billings office. The project files are records specifically related to the buildings the firm was commissioned to design and construct.
Biographical Note
John Gustave Link was born in Bavaria Germany and came to America before 1887. He began working as an architect that year in Denver, Colorado and by the late 1890s he had moved to Montana where he worked in several partnerships including W.E. Donovan, J.C. Paulson, Joseph T. Carter, and Charles S. Haire. The firm of Link and Haire lasted until 1930 when, after Haire’s death, Link formed his own company with two of his sons, J. G. Link, Jr. and Elmer F. Link. The J.G. Link and Company continued operations well up to 1965 and was, at that time, the oldest architectural firm in Montana. The firm had offices in both Billings and Butte, and in the late 1940s employed eighteen persons. They designed both residential and public buildings, many of which are still used in the cities where they are located. John G. Link married Martha M. Welling of St. Louis, Missouri on September 18, 1895 and the couple had six children; Vesta, Randolph, John, Louis, and Elmer. Elmer F. Link (1913-1997) and John Jr. also became architects and Elmer eventually ran the company after his father’s death on January 5, 1954.
The J.G. Link and Company Records consist of photographic images of various building projects, Elmer F. Link’s personal diaries, routine office files and project files. The photographs are either images of the building themselves or of drawings. The diaries are day records of Elmer F. Link. The office files document the day to day operation of the firm, mostly for its Billings office. The project files are records specifically related to the buildings the firm was commissioned to design and construct. The materials have been arranged in four series.
Series 1 Photographs
Series 2 Elmer Link Journals, 1939–1959
Series 3 Office Files, 1949-1965
Series 4 Project Files, 1939-1965
This collection is open for research.
Office files created and maintained by the J.G. Link and Company architectural firm were donated to Montana State University by the Western Heritage Center of Billings, Montana in a series of deposits from 2000 to 2014. These records were donated after many architectural drawings of the firm were accessioned and described by the Special Collections staff and information has been included to link appropriate materials.
Architecture; Billings; Bozeman; Montana; Architecture Drawings; Diaries; Photographs
- Photographs, Series 1
  Primarily photographs of buildings constructed or designed by the J.G. Link and Company Firm. Aerial photographs of named communities and building sites are also included. The photographs have been alphabetically arranged and sequentially numbered. The information in the brackets following the photograph titles represent the collection number and drawing set number that has been previously assigned to architectural drawings by the Special Collections staff of the named building project.
  - #1–12 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - #1–4 Anaconda Gym
      [863; 249]
    - #5 Anaconda High School
      [863; 259]
    - #6–9 Anaconda
    - #10–11 Algeria Shrine
      [2040; 361]
    - #12–12a Assumption Abbey
      [2220; 321]
  - #13–51 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - #13 Beach, North Dakota
    - #14–21 Big Butte Elementary School
      [2219; 041]
    - #22–27 Butte Jr. High School
      [2219; 014]
    - #28–32 Billings Gas Co.
      [2220; 370]
    - #33–34 Bridger School
      [2086; 243]
    - #35 Billings High School
      [863; 253]
    - #36–41 Boulder
    - #42 Billings Electric
    - #43–44 Border Patrol, Havre, Montana
    - #45–46 Behnere Building
    - #47 Blaine Elementary
      [2219; 042]
    - #48–51 Butte Civic Center
      [2219; 012]
  - #52–66 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - #52 Children’s Clinic
    - #53–54 City Hall, Billings
      [863; 255]
    - #55 Civic Center, Helena
    - #56 Carrol College
    - #57 Coulee Dam, Washington
    - #58–59 Cody, Wyoming
    - #60–66 Custer County Court House
  - #67–68 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - #67 Dawson County Courthouse
      [863; 268]
    - #68 Diocese of Great Falls
      [864; 262]
  - #69–80 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - #69–71 East Side School
      [2219; 037]
    - #72–74 Eastern Elementary
    - #75–76 Eberr Apartments
    - #77 Elk’s
    - #78–80 Ekalaka Grade School
      [2060; 020]
  - #8 –90 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - #81–83 Fallon County Hospital
      [863; 182]
    - #84–85 Fairview High School
    - #86 Fairview Gym
      [2060; 023]
    - #87 Fergus County High School
      [863; 079]
    - #88 First National Bank, Butte, Montana
    - #89–90 Forsyth High School
      [2060; 025]
  - #91–131 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - #91–106 Galen
    - #107 Galen, T.B. Hospital
      [2219; 024]
    - #108–110 Galen Receiving Hospital
    - #111–113 Galen Hospital Grounds
    - #114 Galen – Dr. Cole Home
    - #115 Galen, Miscellaneous
    - #116–117 Galen Hospital
    - #118–119 Garfield County Hospital
      [1344; 171]
    - #120–121 Garfield County Courthouse
      [1344; 197]
    - #122–127 Girls Central High School
      [2219; 001]
    - #128 Girls Central, Little Theater
    - #129 Greyhound Bus Department
      [1344; 015]
    - #130 Greyhound Bus
    - #131 Granite City Hospital
      [2219; 009]
  - #132–168 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - #132–133 Headquarters Fire Station
      [2220; 020]
    - #134–138 Holy Name
    - #139–142 Holy Rosary Hospital
      [863; 284]
    - #143 Holy Rosary School
      [1344; 057]
    - #144 Hot Springs, South Dakota
    - #145–151 Home for the Aged
      [2219; 029]
    - #152–167 Humanities Building, University of Montana
      [2219; 033]
    - #168 Holy Name Rectory
      [1344; 044]
  - #169–182 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - #169–173 Immaculate Conception Church
      [863; 035]
    - #174 Immaculate Conception School
      [1344; 023]
    - #175–179 Immaculate Conception Site
    - #180 International Motor Trucks Company
    - #181 International Harvest Company
      [863; 197]
    - #182 Irving School Building
  - #183–188 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - #183–188 Jackson County Courthouse
      [863; 066]
  - #189 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - #189 K.C. Hall
  - #190–193 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - #190 Lewis and Clark County Hospital
      [2040; 046]
    - #191–192 Lewiston Junior High
      [2040; 335]
    - #193 Lockwood Junior High
      [2220; 090]
  - #194–210 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - #194 Masonic Temple, Butte
    - #195–196 Masonic Temple, Billings
      [863; 068]
    - #197 Math and Physics Building, Bozeman
      [1344; 118]
    - #198 Metals Banks
      [2219; 040]
    - #199 Men’s Dorm – Warm Springs
    - #200 Medicine Lake High School
      [2220; 235]
    - #201 Montana State Capital
    - #202 Montana State Board of Health Building
    - #203 Montana State Livestock Building
    - #204–205 Murray’s Motors
    - #206 Musselshell County Court House Site
    - #207–208 Musselshell County Court House
      [863; 174]
    - #209–210 Musselshell County Fairgrounds
  - #211–223 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - #211–213 Northland Service Station
    - #214 Nurses Home, Billings
      [2086; 389]
    - #215–223 Nursing Home
  - #224–228 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - #224–225 Oregon State Capital
    - #226–228 Our Lady of Lourdes Elementary School
  - #229–246 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - #229 Passiley T.B. Hospital
    - #230–241 Pine Hills Prevocational and Maintenance Building
      [2220; 250]
    - #242–246 Powell County High School
      [863; 083]
  - #247–348 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - #247–250 Sacred Heart Hospital
    - #251 Sacred Heart School and Gym
      [1344; 016]
    - #252 Scobey Hospital
      [2219; 031]
    - #253 School of Mines
    - #254–262 Sheridan Law Enforcement
      [2220; 332]
    - #263–267 Silver Bow County Court House
      [863; 279]
    - #268–275 St. Ann’s School
      [1344; 162]
    - #276–289 St. James Hospital
      [863; 212]
    - #290–291 St. Jude’s Church
    - #292–297 St. John’s Hospital
      [2040; 045]
    - #298 St. Joseph’s Hospital
      [863; 109]
    - #299–302 St. Leo’s
      [863; 265]
    - #303–313 St. Margeat’s
    - #314–316 St. Patrick’s Rectory
      [863; 008A]
    - #317 St. Pius
      [1344; 005]
    - #318–320 St. Philenomia
    - #321–340 St. Thomas’s Church
    - #341–343 St. Vincent’s Hospital
      [863; 136]
    - #344–345 St. Vincent’s Academy
    - #346–347 St. Wensclea School
    - #348 Sweet Grass Community Clinic
  - #349–357 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - #349–351 Terry Elementary School
      [1344; 127]
    - #352–356 Trinity High School
      [1344; 158]
    - #357 Timber Apartments
  - #358 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - #358 University of Montana, South and North Hall
  - #359–391 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - #359–364 Valley County WPA Building
    - #365 Valley County Recorders Desk
    - #366–367 Valley County Courtroom Benches
    - #368–370 Valley County – Back of Judges Bench
    - #371–372 Valley County Jury’s Box
    - #373 Valley County Existing Jail
    - #374 Valley County Courtroom
    - #375 Valley County Courthouse – Front
    - #376 Valley County Jail
    - #377–379 Valley County Courthouse
    - #380–391 Veterinary Research Lab
      [1344; 175]
  - #392–442 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - #392–411 Warm Springs
      [2219; 025]
    - #412–422 Webster Garfield
      [2219; 011]
    - #423–425 West Side School, Anaconda
      [863; 180]
    - #426 Western Montana Bank Building
      [2040; 149]
    - #427–429 Whitehall Gym – Proposed
      [2219; 021]
    - #430–431 Wings of the State Capital
    - #432 Wheatland County Hospital
    - #433 WM. K Kones Memorial Library
    - #434 Woman’s Dorm – Montana State University
    - #435–442 Worland High School
  - #443–444 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - #443–444 Yellowstone County Nursing Home
      [2220; 088]
- Elmer Link Journals, 1939–1959; Series 2
  Personal and appointment diaries kept by Elmer F. Link while working in the Billings, Montana office of the J.G. Link and Company In these Journals, Link records the hours he worked on specific projects; the amount of time spent in the office; any traveling he had done; the amount of money spent on these travels as well as the amount of time; phone calls he took that day and with whom those phone calls were with. Along with this, Elmer discusses his personal well-being as well as his personal life. He writes about the weather, parties, and other social events. The diaries have been chronologically arranged by year.
  - 1939 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - 1940 (Box-folder 1/24)
  - 1942 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - 1947 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - 1948 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - 1949 (Box-folder 1/28)
  - 1951 (Box-folder 1/29)
  - 1953 (Box-folder 1/30)
  - 1954 (Box-folder 1/31)
  - 1955 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - 1956 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - 1957 (Box-folder 1/34-35)
  - 1958 (Box-folder 1/36)
  - 1959 (Box-folder 1/37)
- Office Files, 1949-1965; Series 3
  Routine records pertaining primarily to the operation of the Billings office of the J.G. Link and Company firm. Information includes personnel rosters, financial data, application files, and other documents.
  - Applications, 1949; 1950; 1951; 1952; 1953 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Architectural Information – A.I.A. Lic. – Laws Etc., 1947–1958 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Bids – Miscellaneous Jobs (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Brent Wilkens – John Link, 1982 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Building Service (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Business Card Drawings, etc. (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Carol Frost – Janet Thornburg (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Construction Costs – Wage Rates (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Corporation Tax Returns (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Daily Diary (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Descriptions (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Expenses, 1963 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - First National Bank Office Space (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Governments Buildings – Applications – FED. H and H Finance etc., 1953–1958 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Governments Building – Applications for Public Work (Also see Job Promotion), 1949–1953 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - Governments Controls – CMP and PHS forms (Box-folder 2/16)
  - HUD Handbook (Box-folder 2/17)
  - J.G. Link Lawsuit (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Job Promotion, 1933–1945 (Box-folder 2/19)
    – etc.
  - Job Promotion, 1945–1946 (Box-folder 2/20)
  - Job Promotion, 1947 (Box-folder 2/21)
  - Job Promotion, 1948 (Box-folder 2/22)
  - Job Promotion, 1949 (Box-folder 2/23)
  - Job Promotion, 1950–1956 (Box-folder 2/24)
  - Job Promotion, 1959–1961 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Job Promotion – Brochures – Fundraising (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Job Promotion, 1962–1967 (Box-folder 3/3)
    – Correspondence and Notes
  - Job Promotion – Fundraising Information (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Job Promotion and Miscellaneous – Old Letters (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Job Promotion – Office Brochure – Current (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Job Promotion – Photographs (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Job Promotion – Publications (Box-folder 3/8)
  - Job Promotion – Recommendation Letters (Box-folder 3/9)
  - John Link – Susan Axe, 1982 (Box-folder 3/10)
  - John McKittrick – Dale Sickels, 1982 (Box-folder 3/11)
  - Ledger Sheets, 1938–1950 (Box-folder 3/12)
  - Letters of Recommendation (Box-folder 3/13)
  - Larry Marshall – Mike Hefner, 1982 (Box-folder 3/14)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 3/15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958–1961 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Miscellaneous, January 1982 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Miscellaneous Purchases (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Miscellaneous Service Correspondence and Invoices (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Miscellaneous Gov. Forms (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Montana Dakota Utilities, 1963 (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Mutual Help – Bidders – Final (Box-folder 4/9)
  - Office Furniture – Guarantees (Box-folder 4/10)
  - Original Payroll Sheets, 1961–1962 (Box-folder 4/11)
  - Parking Spaces Contract (Box-folder 4/12)
  - Sate Forms – Outdated (Box-folder 4/13)
  - Thomas Shara – Randy Freeck (Box-folder 4/14)
  - Time Sheets Butte, 1959 (Box-folder 4/15)
  - Time Sheets, 1959–1960 (Box-folder 4/16)
    – Leowbridge
  - Time Sheets – B.E. Mazanec, 1960 (Box-folder 4/17)
  - Time Sheets Butte, 1960 (Box-folder 4/18)
  - Time Sheets – Nobles, 1959–1960 (Box-folder 4/19)
  - Time Sheets – Summit, 1960 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - Time Sheets, 1960 (Box-folder 4/21)
  - Tom Regan – Jerry Vielma (Box-folder 4/22)
  - Unemployment Compensation Comm. Rules – Booklet re U.C.C. etc. (Box-folder 4/23)
- Project Files, 1939-1965; Series 4
  Office correspondence, financial data, and other records specifically related to named building projects undertaken by the firm. The information in the brackets following the photograph titles represent the collection number and drawing set number that has been previously assigned to architectural drawings accessioned previously by the Special Collections staff of the named building project. The files have been alphabetically arranged.
  - A. Gerharz, Jr. (Box-folder 5/1)
    [1344; 080]
  - Absarokee High School (Box-folder 5/2)
    [1344; 128]
  - Absarokee School – Stillwater County H.S. Dist. #52, 1951–1954 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - ACME Building Remodel, Billings Montana (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Adams, Dr. and Mrs. Herbert V. Residence – Sheridan Wyoming, 1960–1962 (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Allard Clinic, 1945 (Box-folder 5/6)
    [1344; 020]
  - Alta Club – Miles City (Box-folder 5/7)
    [1344; 071]
  - America Legion Hall – Big Timber (Box-folder 5/8)
    [863; 226]
  - Anaconda School (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Anderson Apartments – Miles City, Montana (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Annunciation Convent of Bismarck, 1954–1955 (Box-folder 5/11)
  - Assumption Abbey – High school, 1954–1958 (Box-folder 5/12)
    [2220; 320]
  - Assumption Abbey – Kitchen – Cafeteria – Dorm - General Correspondence, 1959–1963 (Box-folder 5/13)
  - Assumption Abbey – Kitchen Equipment, Grades, Calculations, Tests, etc., 1960 (Box-folder 5/14)
  - Assumption Abbey Kitchen, Cafeteria, and Dorms – Specifications (Box-folder 5/15)
  - Assumption Abbey – Shop Drawings (Box-folder 5/16)
  - Baylock Laundry (Box-folder 5/17)
  - Baker – Fallon County Hospital (Box-folder 5/18)
  - Beall Pipe and Tank Company, 1945–1953 (Box-folder 5/19)
    [1344; 176]
  - Bennitt, Geo. and Bros. Lewiston Radio Station K.X.L.O. (Box-folder 5/20)
  - Big Timber Gymnasium, 1940–1951 (Box-folder 5/21)
    [1344; 136]
  - Big Timber Gymnasium – Sweet Grass County (Box-folder 5/22)
  - Big Timber Hospital Addition (Sweet Grass Comm. Clinic), 1952–1953 (Box-folder 5/23)
    [1344; 170]
  - Big Timber Grade School (Box-folder 5/24)
    [863; 208]
  - Big Timber Hospital – Progress Reports (Box-folder 5/25)
  - Billings Brewing Company (Box-folder 5/26)
    [863; 194]
  - Billings Central – Remodeling Business Pending (Box-folder 5/27)
  - Billings Elderly Housing II (Box-folder 5/28)
    [2220; 083]
  - Billings Elderly Housing, April 1975 to January 31, 1975 (Box-folder 5/29)
  - Elderly Housing for the City of Billings, through March 1975 (Box-folder 5/30)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Contracts and Statements (Box-folder 5/31)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 5/32)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Correspondence, February 7, 1976 through August 31, 1976 (Box-folder 5/33)
  - Billings Elderly Housing Payroll Records: Collection (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Billings Elderly Housing Working Drawings (Box-folder 6/2)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Miscellaneous (Box-folder 6/3)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Bennett Contracts with all Contractors (Box-folder 6/4)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Inspection Reports (Box-folder 6/5)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Central Electric (Box-folder 6/6)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Frank Pirtz Construction (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Shop Drawings (Box-folder 6/8)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Star Service (Box-folder 6/9)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – Boise – Cascade (Box-folder 6/10)
  - Billings Elderly Housing – General Punch List (Box-folder 6/11)
  - Billings Electric – Store Building (Box-folder 6/12)
  - Billings Federal Courthouse and Office Building – Drawings (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Billings Gas Company (Montana – Dakota Utility), 1946–1956 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Billings School Administration Building – General (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Billings Swimming Pools – Specifications (Box-folder 8/3)
    [2220; 079 and 081]
  - Billings Traffic Bureau (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Billings Turnkey Housing Project – General (Box-folder 8/5)
    [2220; 380]
  - Bonanza, 1966 (Box-folder 8/6)
    [2220; 018] and [1344; 163]
  - Bonanza – Specifications (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Boulder River School and Hospital (Box-folder 8/8)
    [2220; 133]
  - Broadview School Addition, 1959 (Box-folder 8/9)
    [2220; 147 and 149]
  - Brockton – High School Specifications (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Brockton – Working Drawings: Collection (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Brockton – Spec Notes: Collection (Box-folder 8/12)
  - Burke Hotel – Lewiston (Box-folder 8/13)
    [1344; 001]
  - Cartersville School – Rosebud, Montana (Box-folder 8/14)
    [1344; 076]
  - Carter County High School, Ekalaka (Box-folder 8/15)
    [863; 052]
  - Cate Residence, 1973 (Box-folder 8/16)
  - Central Catholic Convent (Box-folder 8/17)
    [2220; 103]
  - Central Convent (Box-folder 8/18)
  - Center for the Aged – Lewiston, Montana (Box-folder 8/19)
    [2220; 225, 226, and 227]
  - Cerebral Palsy Center, 1964 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Chakos Residence (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Chinook – Multi Family Residence (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Circle Bank: Collection (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Cline, F.C., Building 122 North 25th Street (Box-folder 8/24)
    [1344; 149]
  - Crow Agency Schools, 1938–1939 (Box-folder 8/25)
    [2086; 038]
  - Custer County Court House and Jail- Miles City, Montana, 1953 (Box-folder 8/26)
    [2040; 036]
  - Custer County High School – Miles City, Montana (Box-folder 8/27)
    [2040; 011]
  - Daniels Memorial Hospital – Contracts – Progress Reports, 1950–1952 (Box-folder 8/28)
  - Daniels Memorial Hospital – Correspondence – Scobey, Montana (Box-folder 8/29)
  - Daniels Hospital - Scobey, Montana (Box-folder 8/30)
  - Dawson County Jail – Specifications (Box-folder 9/1)
    [2220; 189]
  - D.C. Lochridge Building – Billings, Montana (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Demolition (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Demolition #2 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Demolition #3 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Don Floberg (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Dickinson Golf and Country Club (Box-folder 9/7)
    [2220; 311]
  - Dowdell, Rev, James, Pastor – St. Joseph’s Parish, Anaconda, Montana (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Dr. Fink’s Office – Remodel, 1973 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Dr. Rhodes Residence and Clinic – Sheridan, Wyoming (Box-folder 9/10)
    [1344; 078]
  - East – Montana, Inc. – Roy Dehn – Vic Koch, 1963 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Eastern Montana College of Education – Teachers Laboratory Building – Contracts and Progress Reports, 1952; 1953 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Eastern Montana College of Education – Correspondence and Computation – Teachers Laboratory, Billings, Montana, 1951–1954 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Eastern Montana College of Education – Mechanical (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Eastern Montana College of Education – Structural (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Eastern Montana College of Education – Structural Computations – Wing #1 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Eastern Montana College of Education – Structural Computations – Wing #2 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Eastern Montana College of Education – Structural Computations – Wing #3 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - ECK Building, Lewiston, Montana (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Elks Club – Dillon (Box-folder 9/20)
    [2219; 015]
  - Ennis School (Box-folder 9/21)
    [863; 087]
  - Empire Tire Company, Billings – Harry Wiseman, 1953 (Box-folder 9/22)
    [1344; 018]
  - Empire Tire Company – (Billings Brewery) (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Evans, Bill, 1963 (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Exchange State Bank – Correspondence and Computation – Glendive Montana, 1949–1954 (Box-folder 9/25)
    [1344; 033]
  - Fairview Consolidated Schools (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Fergus County High School VO-AG Building, 1958 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Fire Station - Approvals (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Fire Station No.1 – Correspondence (Box-folder 10/4)
    [2220; 020, 068 and 058]
  - Fire Station No.1 – Contracts and Statements (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Fire Station – Intercom System (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Fire Station #1 – Working Drawings (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Fire Training Center – Contracts, Change Orders, and Payments (Box-folder 10/8)
    [2220; 095]
  - Fire Training Center – Inspection Reports (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Fire Training Center – Travis Jam (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Fire Station Maintenance Building – General Correspondence (Box-folder 10/11)
    [2220; 085]
  - Fire Station Maintenance Building – Alpine Electric (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Fire Station Maintenance Building – Inspection Reports (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Fire Station Maintenance Building – Star Service (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Fire Station Maintenance Building – Travis Jam, Inc. (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Fire Station Maintenance Building – Contracts, Payments and Inspection (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Headquarters Fire Station – Architect’s Field Report (Box-folder 10/17)